

Kamil Dróżdż

Front-end Developer



My Contact

Kamil12x@wp.pl

+48 570728479

Warsaw

https://kamildrozdz.netlify.app/



Skills

★★☆☆☆ React

★★★☆☆ HTML(Metodology BEM)

★★★☆☆ CSS(SASS, Tailwind)

★★★☆☆ Git

★★★☆☆ JavaScript

★★★☆☆ GitHub

★★★☆☆ **RWD**

★★☆☆☆ SEO ★★☆☆ WordPress

★★★☆ Active Listening

★★★☆ The ability to share knowledge

★★★☆ Willingness to constantly learn

Achievements

Programming with JavaScript, Coursera

October 2022

Introduction to Front-End Development, Coursera

October 2022

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures, FreeCodeCamp

October 2022

Certyficate EF SET™, The EF Standard English Test (EF SET)

October 2022

Course basic Javascript, Udemy

September 2022

Increase SEO Traffic with WordPress, Coursera

October 2022

About Me

My goal as a young person is to gain experience, develop organizational and managerial skills as well as change into broadly understood IT, I would like to specialize in programming in Front-end and learn from the best, I broaden my horizons through courses, training, YouTube or making my own projects, sometimes under the supervision of experienced programmers

Experience

Health and safety worker at Twence B.V., Hengelo

August 2017 - April 2018

- Knowledge of labor law and OHS provisions
- Responsibility for colleagues during the joint work,
- Working under time pressure,
- Keeping the workplace clean,
- Team management, supervision over entrusted tasks.

Laundryman at Wasserij Engelbertink, Oldenzaal

June 2017 - August 2017

- · Sorting clothes, bedding,
- Preparing laundry for washing,
- Folding, packing clothes, bedding,
- Operation of washing machines, ironers etc.

Production worker at Wolters B.V., Enter

July 2016 - September 2016

- Palletizing according to the pattern,
- Quality control,
- Maintaining the cleanliness of the station,
- Receiving the finished product,
- Teamwork.

Production worker at Europe Retial Packing, Den Haag

June 2015 - September 2015

- Palletizing according to the pattern,
- Quality control,
- Ensuring compliance with health and safety regulations,
- Close cooperation with management,
- Direct participation in the work of the brigade,
- Motivating and ensuring team development,
- Reporting current activities,
- Securing pallets,
- Notifying superiors about faults,
- Safely operated all equipment and tools.

Education Background

2013 - 2017

• Technical School in Lipno, Lipno Education level: secondary

Specialization: Construction Technician

2019-2021

 Non-public General Secondary School for Adults in Zielonka, Zielonka Education level: secondary

Specialization: Health and Safety

Social Profiles

- <u>LinkedIn</u>
- Github
- Portfolio website